

Deven West

Information Technology
Student

How to reach me:

Cell:

727-647-2231

Email:

Devenw5@gmail.com

devenw@usf.edu

Linkedin:

@devenwest

Github:

@Dreamarchs

Residence:

Clearwater, FL

Personal Profile

I am an Information Technology student looking to get an internship to further my learning and gain valuable experience in my desired field of work.

Educational Training

University of South Florida Graduated July 2021.

Bachelor of Information Technology

- Enrolled since Aug. 2018 to Present. Current GPA 3.05.
- Taking up specialization courses in information technology to broaden skill set.
- Taking up electives in cyber security, and cloud computing.

St. Petersburg College

Associates in Arts

- Attended from Aug. 2015 to
- May 2018.
- Took part in gaming club.

Career Summary

Barista, Cook, Usher

Cobb Theaters

Dec. 2015 to Oct. 2016

Worked many positions like Usher Point of sale, Kitchen, Café.

Took care of guests in a friendly

 and timely manner even during rushes.

Own Website Developed

Created www.DevenWest.com

Created to host my personal

 projects, resume, and anything I find interesting.

Please consider checking it out.

Raymond James Financial

Intern June 2021 – July 2021

 Got experience automating UI testing and working in a DevOps Environment

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

High: C#, Javascript, Java, HTML/CSS/Bootstrap Med: C, Python

Low: Rust

Frameworks/Systems:

High: SQL, Unity, Maven, VSC,

Med: Eclipse, IntelliJ,

Tools:

High: Jenkins, Selenium Box, Med: Jfrog, Docker, SonarQube

Low: APIGee, Gatling

Cobb theatres
Front End Supervisor, Earth Fare
Cell: Message to see this

Jake Thornton

Software Engineer II at EA LinkedIn: @jacobThornton